<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<!--<!DOCTYPE metadata SYSTEM "http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.dtd">-->
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><MetaID>{00CA18D1-666A-11D3-AD23-00C04FA33C50}</MetaID><CreaDate>19990908</CreaDate><CreaTime>20533400</CreaTime><SyncDate>20001208</SyncDate><SyncTime>10394100</SyncTime><ModDate>20001208</ModDate><ModTime>10394100</ModTime><PublishedDocID>{CAC5C7DA-6460-4DA8-ABF1-4227B23FDB0E}</PublishedDocID></Esri><idinfo><native Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows NT Version 4.0 (Build 1381) Service Pack 5; ESRI ArcCatalog 8.1.0.575</native><descript><langdata Sync="TRUE">en</langdata><abstract Sync="TRUE">A brief narrative summary of the data set.  REQUIRED.</abstract><purpose Sync="TRUE">A summary of the intentions with which the data set was developed.  REQUIRED.</purpose></descript><citation><citeinfo><origin Sync="TRUE">The name of an organization or individual that developed the data set.  REQUIRED.</origin><pubdate Sync="TRUE">The date when the data set is published or otherwise made available for release.  REQUIRED</pubdate><title Sync="TRUE">Greenvalley.mxd</title><ftname Sync="TRUE">Greenvalley.mxd</ftname></citeinfo></citation><timeperd><current Sync="TRUE">The basis on which the time period of content information is determined.  REQUIRED.</current><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate Sync="TRUE">The year (and optionally month, or month and day) for which the data set corresponds to the ground.  REQUIRED.</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo></timeperd><status><progress Sync="TRUE">The state of the data set.  REQUIRED.</progress><update Sync="TRUE">The frequency with which changes and additions are made to the data set after the initial data set is completed.  REQUIRED.</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc Sync="TRUE">Western-most coordinate of the limit of coverage expressed in longitude.  REQUIRED.</westbc><eastbc Sync="TRUE">Eastern-most coordinate of the limit of coverage expressed in longitude.  REQUIRED.</eastbc><northbc Sync="TRUE">Northern-most coordinate of the limit of coverage expressed in latitude.  REQUIRED.</northbc><southbc Sync="TRUE">Southern-most coordinate of the limit of coverage expressed in latitude.  REQUIRED.</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt Sync="TRUE">Reference to a formally registered thesaurus or a similar authoritative source of theme keywords.  REQUIRED.</themekt><themekey Sync="TRUE">Common-use word or phrase used to describe the subject of the data set.  REQUIRED.</themekey></theme></keywords><accconst Sync="TRUE">Restrictions and legal prerequisites for accessing the data set.  REQUIRED.</accconst><useconst Sync="TRUE">Restrictions and legal prerequisites for using the data set after access is granted.  REQUIRED.</useconst><natvform Sync="TRUE">Map</natvform></idinfo><metainfo><langmeta Sync="TRUE">en</langmeta><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntper Sync="TRUE">The person responsible for the metadata information.  REQUIRED.</cntper><cntorg Sync="TRUE">The organization responsible for the metadata information.  REQUIRED.</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype Sync="TRUE">The mailing and/or physical address for the organization or individual.  REQUIRED.</addrtype><city Sync="TRUE">The city of the address.  REQUIRED.</city><state Sync="TRUE">The state or province of the address.  REQUIRED.</state><postal Sync="TRUE">The ZIP or other postal code of the address.  REQUIRED.</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice Sync="TRUE">The telephone number by which individuals can speak to the organization or individual.  REQUIRED.</cntvoice></cntinfo></metc><metstdn Sync="TRUE">FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv Sync="TRUE">FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc Sync="TRUE">local time</mettc><metd Sync="TRUE">20001208</metd><metextns><onlink Sync="TRUE">http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink><metprof Sync="TRUE">ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns></metainfo></metadata>
